Imagine an end to crime...
試想想不再有罪案...
...an end to poverty.
不再有貧窮
Imagine 2 million good jobs waiting to be filled.
試想有兩百萬份 令人滿意的工作等著你去做
Sounds like a dream, doesn't it?
聽來像做夢吧
Well, sometimes dreams come true.
有時候夢境會成真
Delta City.
三角洲城
For our children.
為了我們的孩子
This is Media Break. You give us three minutes, we'll give you the world.
這是新聞追擊 給我們三分鐘 我們就給你全世界
Good evening, I'm Casey Wong. Our top story tonight:
晚安 我是凱西·黃 今晚的主要新聞有
Motor City goes Japanese as the Omni Consumer Products Corporation...
數月來的猜測告終 汽車之城變得日本化了
...ended months of speculation today by announcing its takeover...
今天普及消費者產品公司宣佈...
...by the multinational Kanemitsu Corporation.
該公司會被跨國的金光公司收購
Come on, honey, hurry up with your calculus. It's almost time for bed.
乖 你快點把微積分做完 要睡覺了
I'm watching Media Break.
我在看新聞追擊
the first private corporation to completely own and operate a major city.
是第一間私有公司完全擁有和管理 一個大城市的私人機構
Company spokesmen express special interest...
發言人表示對市區...
in the issues of urban resettlement...
重新安置問題 有特別興趣
...and a crime wave in Detroit that many citizens are calling a war zone.
還有底特律的罪案猖獗 市民都叫這做戰區
But as usual, OCP has an answer.
但OCP通常都有解決辦法
Meet the Rehabs, Urban rehabilitation officers.
這些是建改警隊 市區重建改造員警
From the blazing fields of the Amazon War...
從炮火連天的亞馬遜戰場來的
...comes state-of-the-art urban pacification.
新型市區維持治安警隊
We're here to help the people, augment the police force and deal with the gang problem.
我們是來協助市民 增強警方和對付黑道份子
What about reports you're actually evicting people...
有報導說 你們其實是來驅逐居民...
...to make way for construction of Delta City?
以便興建三角洲城的
Nikko, you heard your mom. Go on.
妮歌 聽媽媽的話 來吧
Oh, man.
哎
- And the homeless?  - What a gyp.
- 無家可歸的人又怎樣  - 真滑頭
Some buildings have to come down before Delta can go up.
要拆毀一些建築物 才能興建三角洲城
I won't deny we're serving an eviction notice or two...
我不否認我們發了一兩張驅逐令...
...but most of these people have already taken their urine tests and placement exams.
但大部分人都接受過 驗尿和入職考試
They've got new jobs waiting for them.
有新工作等著他們做的
We're just helping them make the transition, that's all.
我們只是在過渡時期協助他們
- We're cops, nothing more.  - Nothing more?
- 我們是員警 別無其他  - 別無其他
Well, we're not robots, if that's what you mean.
我的意思是 我們不是機械人
Hey, Dad?
爸爸
You're supposed to be asleep.
你該睡了
Is it true what the Tv said?
電視說的是不是真的
That it's a war zone outside?
外面是不是有個戰區
Don't listen to what the Tv says. This is your home, you hear me?
別聽電視說的 這裡是你的家 知道嗎
And you're safe here.
你在這裡很安全
I'll buy that for a dollar!
付多少錢我也願意
Get out, get out, get out!
快走...
（驅逐令）
This neighborhood is the property of omni Consumer Products.
這一區是普及消費者產品公司的資產
底特律
卡迪拉克區
機械戰警3
- For God's sake, help us!  - That's what we're here for, ma'am.
- 天啊 幫幫我們  - 我們正是來幫你們
Just get on the bus.
上車
Where are they taking us, Dad? What's happening?
爸爸 他們帶我們去哪裡 發生什麼事
Don't believe them! They'll throw us into the streets to die like rats!
別相信他們 他們會丟我們到街上 自生自滅
Nazi sons of bitches!
納粹党混蛋
Shoot her if you must, but get her out of here.
有需要時就射死她 但把她帶走
Yes, sir.
知道
Let's go. Come on.
走吧
I think it's going rather well, don't you?
我認為進展得不錯 是不是
Yes, sir.
是的
Come on, I said, move! Move!
我叫你快點 走吧
- Manandle an old lady, would you?  - Shut up!
- 你對老婦粗暴點 好嗎  - 閉嘴
- Move, move!  - Get up there!
- 走  - 上車
I said, get up!
我叫你起來
What are you doing down there? Piece of slime!
你在下麵幹嘛 笨蛋
Can you hear me?
聽到我說嗎
I said, get up, you drunken cow!
我叫你起來 笨蛋
Get back! The crane's gonna blow!
退後 那架起重機會爆炸
Listen to me, people! These buses are going nowhere!
大家聽著 這些巴士那兒也去不了
Stay here! Fight for your homes! There is no silver lining!
留下來 為你們的家園抗爭 根本不會有好日子
Only corporate scumbags who want to line their pockets!
只是那些機構混蛋想中飽私囊
Nikko! Nikko!
妮歌 ...
Mom! Mom! Dad!
媽媽 爸爸
Nikko! No! That's my baby! Nikko, Nikko!
妮歌 不 那是我的孩子 妮歌
Mom! Dad! Dad!
媽媽 爸爸
Mom, Dad!
Mom!
媽媽
Dad?!
爸爸
Mom!
媽媽
You! Stay where you are!
你 別走開
Repeat: The rehabilitation officers are here to assist you.
重複 建改警隊是來協助你們的
It's okay, it's okay. You're with us now.
沒事的 你現在跟我們一起
Is he gone?
他走了沒有
Are we clear?
我們是否安全
Clear!
安全
Okay, let's do it.
好 我們來吧
Okay, Moreno.
好了 莫連奴
Cover your ears.
掩著耳朵
Rock 'r roll.
來吧
All clear. Let's go.
沒有人 我們走吧
Jesus!
天啊
- ED 209!  - He wasrt in the recon photo!
- ED209  - 他不在偵察照片裡
Freeze! You are trespassing on police property.
別動 你們擅自闖進警方範圍
Please surrender your weapons.
放下武器
- What the hell?  - Is she crazy?
- 什麼事  - 她瘋的嗎
You have 20 seconds to comply.
你們有二十秒時間
- Hey, kid, come back here!  - You're gonna get us all killed!
- 孩子 回來  - 你會害死我們的
What the hell is she doing?
她到底在幹什麼
You are in direct violation of penal code 114, section 3.
你們直接違反了法例第114條 第3節
I am authorized to use physical force.
我有權使用武力
You now have 10 seconds to comply.
你們現在有十秒時間
You won't believe this. He'll be loyal as a puppy.
你們不會相信的 他會像頭小狗般忠心
You have five seconds. Four seconds.
你們有五秒 四秒...
Three seconds. You have one second to comply.
三秒 你們有一秒時間
I am now authorized to...
我現在有權...
...be loyal as a puppy.
像頭小狗般忠心
Damn!
厲害
Will it work?
會有效嗎
Stole it off a dead cop.
從一個死了的員警偷來的
（有人闖入）
Holy shit! That's the police armory!
該死 是警方軍火庫
- They deleted the access signature.  - Let's get out of here!
- 他們取消了通行識認  - 我們快走
They'll be a few minutes. Let's figure out how to open that door!
他們幾分鐘後才到達 我們想辦法打開這扇門
Are you kidding me?
你開玩笑吧
One-stop shopping.
一站式購物呢
- Let's go! Gotta get out of here!  - He's right. Let's ride.
- 快走 要立刻離開  - 走
- What are you, picking out drapes?  - Coming!
- 你幹嘛 選窗簾布  - 來了
- Get that.  - Why?
- 拿那個  - 為什麼
It looks expensive.
它看來很昂貴
Come on! Come on, let's go!
我們走吧
Drop your weapons now!
放下武器
Do it! Drop them!
快點 放下武器
Freeze! You're trespassing on police property.
別動 你們擅自闖進警方範圍
Eat lead, suckers!
混蛋 去死吧
Nikko, get in! Come on!
妮歌 快上車
What can I do for you?
有什麼可效勞
Nobody move!
別動
Everything in the register! Now! Do it!
把收銀機裡的錢拿來 快點
What's it like being a rocket scientist?
當火箭科學家是什麼滋味
All units, we have a B and E involving police property, please respond.
所有單位注意 警方範圍裡發生破門闖入事件 請回應
Repeat, all units, we have a...
重複 所有單位注意...
Hey, Donnelly, it's your turn.
唐諾利 輪到你了
- No way. We went last time.  - No, it's Lewis' turn.
- 不行 我們上次去了  - 不 輪到路易士
Lewis, you're up.
路易士 到你去
Lewis! Lewis! Lewis!
路易士...
Isn't anybody gonna arrest me, or what?!
究竟有沒有人要拘捕我
- Where's your friend Murphy?  - He's not big on doughnuts.
- 你朋友墨菲去了哪裡  - 他不喜歡吃甜甜圈的
- He's not big on doughnuts.  - I knew that.
- 他不喜歡吃甜甜圈  - 我知道
All units, repeat, that is a battered yellow van.
所有單位注意 重複 是一輛殘舊的黃色小型貨車
No plates. Tracking shows southbound...
沒有牌照 追蹤器顯示朝南面走
- That's a battered yellow van.  - No shit, Sherlock.
- 那是輛殘舊的黃色小型貨車  - 不錯
Moreno, company's coming!
莫連奴 我們有伴了
Hold on. Here we go.
抓穩點 來吧
Unit 477 in pursuit, eastbound, Esposito.
單位477正在追蹤 朝東面艾蒲賽道走
Watch it!
小心
I'm watching it!
我很小心
Jesus!
天啊
They're still on our tail.
他們還追著我們
Don't sweat it.
不用怕
Hey, kid. Watch this.
孩子 看這個
Hold the champagne.
別高興得太早
You stopped in the middle of the street!
你停在馬路中心
- That was my light!  - You idiot!
- 我是綠燈  - 笨蛋
- Is everybody okay?  - Okay? What are you, a comedian?
- 大家沒事吧  - 沒事 你說笑嗎
I traded in a brand new SUX for this classic. Now look at it!
我用一輛全新SUX換的 看看
It's garbage. It's going to the junkyard.
真是垃圾 去廢車場好了
What is this, fellas? You give a broad a badge and she gets delusions of gander.
這是什麼 給婆娘一個徽章 她就以為自己是老闆
It's "grandeur," dumbshit.
是權勢 笨蛋
This new guy is making me nervous.
這個新人令我緊張
I don't think this is exactly a guy.
我相信這不是人類
You think it's him?
是不是他
Unit 477 to dispatch.
單位477叫調遣部
This is 477 to dispatch. Come in, dispatch.
477叫調遣部 請通話
We could use some backup out here.
我們需要支援
Hello, dispatch. Come in. This is 477 to dispatch.
調遣部 請通話 這是477
Lewis.
路易士
Splatterpunks.
霹靂黨
Wait a second, what do you need the shotgun for?
等一下 你們拿著機關槍幹嘛
Shit, we're all gonna die.
我們都要死了
- Sit tight, people. Backup's coming.  - Sit tight?
- 別動 支援快到了  - 別動
If it wasrt for you, I wouldn't even be here, you dumb broad.
要不是你 我也不會在這裡 笨婆娘
I'll make you a deal, tough guy. You want to eat the tie, keep it up.
我跟你作個協議 你想吃掉領帶就繼續鬧吧
Take it easy. My brother's a cop.
放鬆點 我哥哥是個員警
距離113.7碼
聲音分析
477 to dispatch, code 3! We're low on ammo and need immediate backup!
477叫調遣部 緊急事故 我們子彈不足 需要支援
安妮·路易士
編號
備份請求
Right now!
馬上來
Sergeant Reed.
瑞德警官
I got Murphy's cruiser on the grid.
我在位置圖上看到墨菲的巡邏車
- He just turned around.  - He what?!
- 他剛調頭了  - 什麼
Murphy, this is Reed.
墨菲 我是瑞德
I have three other vehicles en route to Lewis.
我派了三輛車去聲援路易士
Murphy, continue pursuit! That is a direct order! Do I make myself clear?
墨菲 繼續追蹤 這是個直接命令 明白嗎
Murphy, are you listen...?
墨菲 你是否聽...
Police officer. No loitering.
員警 不准遊蕩
You called for backup?
你需要支援
Thanks for dropping by, Murphy.
謝謝你來 墨菲
Are they gone?
他們走了沒有
I'm still scanning three.
我掃描到還有三個人
Make that two.
剩下兩個人
Block it! Megazone invasion!
快躲避 大攻擊來了
Pop a tranq, hypo-head. Splatterville's ours.
冷靜點 笨蛋 霹靂圍是我們的
Shoot him in the mouth.
射他的嘴
Cyborg eats bullets, Jock.
半機械人要吃子彈了
Not tonight he don't.
今晚他不吃
Hit him in the mouth!
射他的嘴
- Shut up!  - Do it! Do it!
- 閉嘴  - 做吧
- Do it! Do it!  - Shut up!
- 做吧  - 閉嘴
Nice try, creeps.
試得好 變態鬼
Give me it!
給我
You have the right to remain silent.
你們有權保持緘默
Down there.
在那邊
Jesus, Murphy, are you okay?
天啊 墨菲 你沒事吧
I'm fine, Anne.
我很好 安妮
Thank you for asking.
謝謝關心
Come on, come on!
快點...
Let's go! Everything will be all right.
快走 不會有事的
Get your damn hands off me!
放手
Stupid kid.
笨孩子
錄影中
- Come here. Come on.  - Would you forget the stupid kid already?!
- 過來  - 你別管那個孩子好嗎
錄影中
無能的美國人
你們又肥又懶惰
現在不單是錢財上受到威脅
你越犯大錯...
我們的競爭對手就越笑得大聲
你們的行動令我們雙方蒙羞
Kanemitsu-san...
金光先生
...I realize we've had setbacks...
我知道我們遭受挫折
...but we've done everything possible to get Delta City back on schedule.
但我們已經盡一切努力 讓三角洲城如期復工
你們的能力都表露無遺了
我會派一個特工來修正你們的錯誤
Gentlemen...
各位...
...you are now looking at a company...
本公司正面臨...
...in transition.
過渡時期
Needless to say, this has resulted in the implementation of certain...
不用說 這樣做已導致執行上某些...
...well...
嗯
...let's call them...
我們稱它們為...
..."cutbacks."
削減
But who can put a price tag on a dream?
但誰能為夢想估價
Our esteemed former chairman had a dream.
我們受人敬重的前主席 有一個夢想
He called it Delta City.
他叫它做三角洲城
Knock it off, Johnson.
別這樣 強生
The great city of Detroit represents an important precedent, gentlemen.
各位 偉大的底特律市代表著一個重要的先河
There's only one small problem.
但有一個小問題
It's turning into a war zone!
它變成了一個戰區
It's just a small resistance group.
是個小規模反抗組織罷了
There's no reason to believe they pose a significant threat.
他們不會構成重大威脅
I'd consider...
我認為...
...a deficit of 350 million dollars a significant threat.
三億五千萬元的赤字 是個重大威脅
Wouldrt you?
是不是
- Fleck!  - Sir.
- 費曆克  - 先生
You're in charge of Security Concepts.
你主管保安概念部
Where's that Robocop we spent so much money on?
我們耗資巨大的機械員警在哪裡
The police had a problem with the unit. I'm dealing with it personally.
警方對那個裝置有問題 我正在處理
You do that.
你快做
Get him to the Rehab Team...
派他去建改組
...and maybe we won't have to worry about a "small resistance group."
我們也許就不用擔心 一個小規模反抗組織了
Get the hell out of here, all of you!
你們快滾出去
You take your time.
你們慢慢來
And for God's sake, Fleck...
天啊 費曆克...
...try to get the police on our side.
嘗試拉攏警方幫我們
What if I don't want a robot on my team?
若我不想有個機械人在我隊中呢
You've got 4 days, McDaggett.
保羅麥代格 你有四天時間
If Cadillac Heights isn't cleared for demolition Friday midnight...
若卡迪拉克區在週五淩晨 還未清場進行拆毀...
...our loans will be called in. OCP will be ruined.
我們會被追討貸款 OCP就會完蛋
We made a deal, didn't we, chum.
我們有個協議的 是嗎
Oh, by the way...
順便一提...
...if you're just figuring out the line between big business and war...
如果你覺得做大生意和作戰的界線...
...is a little blurry...
有點模糊不清...
...then you're further over the hill than they say.
那麼你就是 比他們口中說得好要糟
金光世界總部
但是 金光先生
我們從沒派過雄志去這麼人口稠密的地區
不要再討論了
西區警察局
This is entrapment! My client was visiting close friends in that motel.
這是誘捕 我的當事人當時在那間旅館探訪朋友
Hey, buddy. Your client's friends...
你當事人的朋友們...
...were a non-union video crew and a German shepherd.
是一支非工會攝影組和一頭德國牧羊狗
That's prejudicial.
那有偏見
Did the arresting officer ask to see their union cards?
那個負責拘捕的警員有否要求看他們的工會證
Come get this crap. Will someone answer the damn phone?!
來處理這個 聽電話好嗎
Metro West. No, ma'am, we're not on strike.
西區 不 小姐 我們沒有罷工
You could have fooled me. I'll deal with those looters myself.
你本可以騙倒我 我會處置那班劫匪
Get me a baseball bat with some nails in it.
給我一支有釘的壘球棒
How are you feeling?
你覺得怎樣
I've been better.
不大好
To be honest, it looks like you just made friends with a Mack truck.
老實說 你像跟一輛貨車做了朋友
I don't have many...
我沒有很多...
...friends.
朋友
Dr. Lazarus.
賴莎拉斯博士
- You want to tell me what happened?  - Atlanta beat the Pistons last night.
- 發生了什麼事  - 阿特蘭大隊昨晚打贏活塞隊
- That's cute. I meant with glory boy.  - Oh, him.
- 很有趣 我是指英勇小子  - 是他
He got shot to hell and set on fire.
他受到槍擊 還著了火
You know what I'm talking about. He disobeyed a direct order. Why?
你明白我的意思 他違抗直接命令 為什麼
- My real opinion?  - No, lie. Make up a story.
- 我真正的意見  - 不 說謊 編個故事
Well, Mr. Fleck...
費曆克先生...
...offhand...
目前...
...l'd say the only reason he'd disobey an order is if...
我認為他抗命的唯一理由是...
...he didn't agree with it.
他不同意那個命令
Excuse me?
什麼
He made a decision.
他作了一個決定
His friend was in trouble, he made a judgment call. Cops do that.
他的朋友有麻煩 他作出判斷 員警都那樣做的
Human cops. What do you mean, "his friend"? It's a machine.
人類的員警 你說"他的朋友"是什麼意思 它是副機器
Look,
聽著
if oCP just wanted a robot, why'd they put Murphy in there in the first place?
如果OCP只要一個機械人 為何他們派墨菲去那裡
Murphy's dead, sweetheart, that's on record.
墨菲已經死了 已有記錄在案
Mr. Fleck, this is Murphy!
費曆克先生 這就是墨菲
What's left of his face, his cerebrum, his cerebellum.
在他的面孔 大腦 小腦所留下的
Human tissue that's still alive.
人體組織仍然存在
How can you interface human and machine...
為何結合兩者...
then complain when the human part makes a decision?
但當人類部分作決定時又要抱怨
So not only did we get Murphy's years of training...
那麼我們不但得到了墨菲多年來的訓練...
and his law-enforcement skills, we also inerited...
和執法技巧 還繼承了...
...his memories, his feelings, his emotional baggage?
他的記憶 感覺和情緒
Well, I'd call it his humanity, but I don't think you know that word.
我會叫它做他的人性 但我相信你不認識那個字眼
I see.
是吧
You talked me into it. His emotions: Get rid of them.
你說服我了 刪除他的情感
Find their location and erase them. If it wipes out his memory, too bad.
找出它們的位置後消除它們 如果洗掉他的記憶 那真糟糕
We could cut out the appropriate circuits by...
我們可以植入一個 微型神經障礙器...
...implanting a micro-neuro-barrier.
截斷有關的線路
Do it.
做吧
I got news for you. I don't give a shit how smart you are.
聽著 我不管你有多聰明
OCP owns the cops. That means they own him, and they own your cute little ass.
OCP擁有警隊 擁有他 還擁有你
Nobody owns me.
沒有人能擁有我
Fine.
很好
We want him on the Rehab Team.
我們要他加入建改隊
That means you make him predictable, or look for a new job, sweet cheeks.
你把他改為可以預測 否則你另謀高就
I think I'm in love.
我墮入愛河了
What's going through your head?
你腦海中想著什麼
（記憶搜尋：墨菲）
That's his family.
那是他的家人
Want me to install the neuro-barrier, doctor?
可要我安裝那個神經障礙器
No, I can do it.
不 我可以做
I think I'd like to be alone with him, if it's all right.
我想單獨陪著他
（記憶搜尋：墨菲）
Alex, I thought you'd never get home.
墨菲 我以為你永遠不回來了
Don't let the fact that these people are homeless sway you.
別讓那些無家可歸的人動搖你們
They're terrorists, pure and simple.
他們都是恐怖分子
On the screens are suspected rebel locations.
畫面上的都是可疑的叛軍位置
If these locations appear on your regular beat, check it out.
若這些地點在你們的巡邏範圍內 便去查看一下
Make sure you report any unusual findings...
報告任何不尋常的發現...
Hear what they did to Murphy?
有聽到他們怎樣處置墨菲嗎
重 播
Murphy.
墨菲
Lewis, you want your body armor?
路易士 要不要盔甲
What? No, I'm off duty.
什麼 不要 我下班了
What's up, anyway?
到底什麼事
Do you have family?
你有沒有家人
Yeah, I have a brother in Pittsburgh, the one who never calls. You know that.
有 有個在匹茲堡 從不打電話給我的弟弟 你知道的
Robo, are you okay?
機械人 你沒事吧
I'm fine.
我很好
And call me Murphy.
叫我墨菲
熱能圖像
Murphy?
墨菲
Step out of the building.
離開這座建築物
Stay right there.
留在原地
We're police officers.
我們是員警
We don't want you.
我們不需要你們
We believe there are squatters in there. Now step away from the door.
裡面有一些擅闖者 別靠近那扇門
They're civilians. They're just trying to stay warm!
他們是平民 他們想取暖罷了
Those people belong in the nearest rehabilitation center.
這些人是屬於一所改造中心的
1>為公眾服務
首要指令:
Some are terrorists. Step away or you will be cited for obstructing justice.
部分是恐怖分子 走開 否則你會被控阻礙辦公
2>保護無辜者
首要指令:
I'm not going to ask politely next time.
我不會再禮貌地要求了
首要指令:
Step away from the door.
別靠近那扇門
3>執行法紀
This is your final warning.
這是你們的最後警告
4>不准違抗OCP人員
首要指令:
You are making a mistake.
你們犯了個錯誤
- Back off, or there'll be trouble.  - Now you're talking, Murphy.
- 退後 否則會有麻煩  - 這樣才對
We're not budging. If you wanna get in, you'll have to shoot through us.
我們不會讓步 你們開槍射我們吧
I don't have a huge problem with that.
我不覺得那有大問題
瞄準中
4>不准違抗OCP人員
Cease fire!
停火
系統損毀警報 效率72%
Robocop.
機械員警
系統損毀警報 效率69%
Come on, come on, come on!
快 快 快
Come with us!
跟我們走吧
Cover me.
掩護我
Some tough cop I am. Huh, partner?
我是個精銳的員警 是不是 夥伴
I'm scared.
我很害怕
Don't be.
不要怕
It won't hurt long.
不會痛太久的
記 錄
Get them for me.
替我抓他們
Promise me.
答應我
I promise.
我答應你
Murphy.
墨菲
Officer down.
警員身亡
Move it!
快走
We don't have much time.
沒時間了
Nikko, let's go.
妮歌 我們走吧
Come on. Come with us.
快點 跟我們走
Is she crazy? He's a cop! He's one of them!
他是個員警 是他們的人
He's on our side now.
他現在是我們的人
She's right. You saw what he did.
她說得對 你看到他做的事
You'll let a stupid kid make our decisions?
你讓個笨小孩替我們作決定
- We're at war. We can use his help.  - Are you kidding me? Look at him!
- 我們去作戰 我們需要他幫忙  - 你說笑嗎 看他
He is totaled, man!
他毀爛不堪
People, come on. We don't have time for this shit.
來吧 沒時間爭論了
He's right.
他說得對
We should go.
我們該走了
Five-meter spread. Search the perimeter.
在五米範圍內周圍搜索
Damn.
該死
- We're tracking him, sir. He's moving.  - Impossible. The building is surrounded.
- 長官 他在移動  - 不可能的 整個建築物都被包圍了
He's gone underground.
他走到地下去了
Find a manole.
找個入口
We got a little held up.
我們有點阻礙
Rats?
老鼠
One or two.
一兩隻吧
熱能圖像
Go on through.
走過去
系統損毀警報 效率25%
Are you okay?
你沒事吧
I'm fine.
我很好
Hey!
你
You guys!
你們快來
Oh, man!
天啊
I told you it was a mistake to bring him.
我叫你不要帶他來的
I bet he weighs a ton.
他重得要命
Watch your step.
小心
All right.
好吧
Clear the way.
讓開
- Get out of the way.  - Hold up your side.
- 讓開  - 扶著你那一邊
He don't look good.
他看來不妙
You wouldn't look so good either if you took a grenade in your chest.
你胸口中了手榴彈也會不妙
Tracking.
追蹤
- Beacon.  - Tracking?
- 信標  - 追蹤
He'll lead them right to us!
他會帶領他們找到來的
Shut up, Coontz!
閉嘴 康斯
What's he talking about?
他在說什麼
- Did he booby-trap the 8th Street entrance?  - Maybe.
- 他可有在入口設下陷阱  - 可能吧
Better get mobilized, folks.
我們還是快走
They got a little too close to home that time.
那次他們幾乎得手
It's not won'th it.
這是不值得的
It's not won'th this shit!
根本不值得
You better take a real deep breath right now, Coontz.
你最好深深吸一口氣
Because if you don't think it's won'th it...
因為如果你認為這樣不值得...
...then you're nothing but excess baggage. Do you hear me?!
你就死定了 明白嗎
You get it together, Coontz.
你想清楚
Cadillac Heights may not be much, but it's our home.
卡迪拉克區可能不算得什麼 但它是我們的家
It's all we got.
我們只有它
If you don't think our homes is won'th it, then tell me what the hell is.
如果你認為我們的家園不值得 告訴我什麼才值得
This is Bertha to Base op. We're coming in.
貝黛叫基地行動組 請通話
Set an extra place.
設置一個新地方
We're bringing in a friend.
我們會帶一個朋友來
Incoming caller.
有來電
What do you want?
你想怎樣
Nice work, dollface.
美人 做得好
What you talking about?
你是什麼意思
You haven't heard?
你沒聽到嗎
You might want to turn on Media Break.
不如看看新聞追擊吧
Tv on, channel 378.
開電視 378頻道
Witness to the tragic shooting was Rehab Commander, Paul McDaggett.
目擊這次悲慘開槍事件的 是建改隊指揮官保羅·麥代格
All I can say is it's a terrible loss of a fine public servant.
我只能說 這次損失了一個良好的公僕
It's hard to believe that she was gunned down by her own partner.
她被自己的夥伴射死 真是難以置信
An OCP spokesperson has confirmed...
OCP發言人證實
that Robocop has joined the terrorist rebel forces.
機械員警已經加入了叛軍
He is heavily armed and should be considered extremely dangerous.
他擁有大量武器 是個危險人物
Tv off.
關電視
Congratulations, sweet cheeks. Now listen up. I want your legendary ass...
恭喜你 美人兒 聽著 我要你...
...and your corporate I.D. Card in my office...
帶著你的工作證到我的辦公室
And maybe you won't be brought up on charges.
你不會被起訴
Meantime, you might want to decide whose side you're on.
你考慮一下你要幫哪一邊吧
Sleep tight.
晚安
（通話完畢 通話時間一分三秒）
- He what?  - Shot at Rehabs and went underground.
- 他什麼  - 向建改隊開槍和做地下工作
- There goes our P.R. Budget.  - Company line is he's gone renegade.
- 我們的公關預算泡湯了  - 公司說他叛變了
- How'd the CEO take it?  - How do you think?
- 總管有何反應  - 你認為會怎樣
Between me and you, I think the CEO's losing it.
我跟你說 總管很生氣
I mean, take a look around, will you?
看看周圍
It's the Fall of Rome around here.
這裡像羅馬帝國倒臺一樣
It's Darwin time, you know what I'm saying?
岌岌可危 你明白嗎
Survival of the least expendable.
有用的才能生存
Remember the old man. Everyone's expendable.
記得舊老闆吧 所有人都可以被犧牲
It can't be that bad.
不是那麼糟糕的
Honey, can you hear me?
親愛的 你聽到嗎
Are you there?
你在嗎
Every corporation goes through this sort of thing.
每間公司都有這個情況的
Oh, my God, what happened?
天啊 發生了什麼
What's happening?
發生什麼事
Arnott just went out the window.
阿諾跳樓了
- That's the fourth one this month.  - Chickenshit.
- 那是本月的第四宗  - 膽小鬼
I'd eat a bullet myself.
我會選擇吞槍自殺
Less showy.
沒那麼張揚
The writing was on the wall the minute we hopped...
我們跟那間混帳金光公司合作的那一刻
...in the sack with that shitty Kanemitsu corporation.
就已經心知肚明
As I was saying...
正如我說...
...we have a warrant out for Robocop's arrest.
我們有捉拿機械員警的拘捕令
If we can eliminate him, then we'll find that the squatters are more...
如果我們把他剷除 我們認為那些擅闖者...
...let's say, easily persuaded.
就更容易被說服
- Fleck!  - Sir.
- 費曆克  - 先生
I'm sorry for the intrusion, sir.
老闆 抱歉打擾你
Anything Security Concepts can do?
保安概念部有什麼可以做的
Security Concepts can kiss my freckled butt. You're fired.
保安概念部可以去死 你被開除了
You heard me! You're fired. Get out of here.
你聽到吧 你被開除了 滾
Three days until disaster.
三天后就有大災難
What the hell will I tell my shareholders?
我怎樣向股東們解釋
What about more Rehabs, sir?
增加建改隊人手如何
We could recruit them out of the Police Department.
我們可以從員警部招募的
It would be cheaper than mercenaries...
他們比雇傭兵更便宜
...and we could use the Metro West facility as a staging area.
我們可以利用西區警察局作試點
Give them a nominal raise for an incentive.
給他們象徵式的加薪以作鼓勵
You're a good man, Johnson.
強生 你是個好人
I knew there was a reason I made you a vice president.
我知道我提升你做副總裁是有原因的
Thank you, sir.
過獎 老闆
I really...
我真的...
（暴虐的資本主義蠢豬）
Heads up!
接著
Come on, let's go. We're gonna be late!
快點 我們要遲到了
Well?
怎樣
Can you fix him?
你能否修理他
This isn't a valve job on a Chevy.
這不是修理汽車活門
I never worked on a damn Robocop before.
我從沒修理過機械員警
- I can do the body work, but...  - Look...
- 我可以修理機身 但是...  - 聽著
...we gotta hang on to the Heights for three more days.
我們要多保衛著卡迪拉克區三天
- He can hold out till then, can't he?  - Are you listening to me?!
- 他能否支持到那時  - 你有沒有聽我說
He's messed up. We don't have the equipment.
他損毀嚴重 我們也沒有儀器
Who the hell does?!
誰有
Lazarus.
賴莎拉斯
Find doctor...
去找...
Lazarus.
賴莎拉斯
Who are you?
你是誰
I'm friends with Robocop.
我是機械員警的朋友
Well, he's not here. I'm sorry.
他不在這裡 抱歉
You don't believe me.
你不相信我
To tell you the truth, I don't know what to believe anymore.
坦白說 我不知道該相信什麼
He had a message for you.
他要我帶個話給你
He said to thank you for not taking his memories away.
他說感謝你沒有洗掉他的記憶
Well, well, well.
好...
Afraid you're a little late, pal.
恐怕你來遲一步了
You must be one of Kanemitsu's boys.
你一定是金光的人
I'm impressed.
我很欽佩
Trouble is...
問題是...
...your boss...
你的老闆...
...he kind of owns oCP.
他擁有OCP
And oCP's kind of on our shitlist with a bullet!
而OCP是我們的死對頭
So you want to know where the rebels are?
你想知道叛軍在哪裡
You can tell your bosses to kiss my ass!
你可以叫你的老闆去死
A vehicle is approaching.
有一輛車正在駛近
How you doing, Murphy?
墨菲 你好嗎
I've been better.
不大好
- Give me a status scan.  - Organics intact.
- 給我一個狀態掃描  - 生物體沒有受損
Systems efficiency: 23 percent.
系統效率23%
Looks like a direct hit to the heart.
心臟直接受撞擊
We have to recalibrate the pneumatic system.
我們要重新調校充氣系統
Is he gonna die?
他會不會死
Not if I can help it.
我幫到它就不會的
Let's get everything hooked up to the generator.
接到發電機吧
We've got work to do.
我們有工作要做
I'm going to unplug you for a little while.
聽這 我要暫時關掉你的能源
系統損毀警報 效率12%
Don't worry, everything's gonna be okay.
放心 不會有事的
Here you go.
拿著
I got that heart you wanted.
我找到你要的那個心臟
I said a Nissan. That's a Kanemitsu.
我說要日產 那是金光
Zack, we need that sealant! Zack!
澤克 我們要那支密封膠 澤克
Marie! Marie! Look!
瑪莉... 看
Oh, shit.
不好了
Bring me that chest plate over here.
拿那塊胸部金屬板來
You wait, man.
等一會
You are gonna be so cherry.
你會沒事的
Moreno, watch out for the...
莫連奴 小心那個...
What the hell are you doing?
你幹什麼
I didn't know that thing was there!
我不知道那東西在那裡
- Don't yell at me!  - Well, don't do it.
- 別向我大叫  - 那麼 不要那樣做
首要指令
1>為公眾服務
2>保護無辜者
3>執行法紀
4>不准違抗OCP人員
4>已被刪除
Murphy.
墨菲
It's you.
是你
Alex, I thought you'd never get home.
墨菲 我以為你永遠不會回來了
指令記憶設定 系統狀態良好
Welcome home, Murphy.
墨菲 歡迎你
I couldn't sleep.
我睡不著
How are you feeling?
你覺得怎樣
My efficiency rate is 93 percent.
我的效率現在是93%
Anything above 90 is considered normal.
90以上都是正常
I heard Marie call you Murphy.
我聽到瑪莉叫你做墨菲
Is that your real name?
那是你的真名字嗎
It was...
以前是的...
...before...
之前...
Before what?
之前什麼
So...
所以
Now that you're better, will you stay?
你現在復原了 你會留下來嗎
Will you help us?
你會不會幫我們
You know what Bertha says. If we hold back the Rehabs for two more days...
你知道貝黛說什麼吧 若我們抵抗建改隊多兩天...
...they can't make us move.
他們就不能逼我們搬遷
And they'll have to let my parents go. We'll all be together like family again.
他們就要釋放我爸媽 我們會一家團聚
Your parents?
你的爸媽
（身亡）
Murphy? You okay?
墨菲 你沒事吧
Your parents, you miss them?
你想念他們嗎
Yeah.
想念
But...
但是...
...you remember them.
你記著他們
Because...
因為...
...if you remember them...
如果你記著他們...
...they're never really gone.
他們就沒有真正離開過
Hey, Murphy...
墨菲...
...l'm glad your new heart works.
我很高興你新的心臟有效
I heard voices.
我聽到一些聲音
She should be in bed.
她該上床睡了
Could you leave her...
她可以再留...
...just a moment?
一會兒嗎
Of course.
當然可以
You gotta pay for that.
你要付錢的
What are you, deaf?
你聾的嗎
Son of a...
混...
That's not what we said.
我們不是那麼說的
It's not what we said we were gonna do!
我們不是說要那樣做的
Bertha, you said to relocate the weapons...
你說要遷移那些武器
...but where do you want this thing?
但這東西要放在哪裡
Oh, my God.
我的天
How did you get this?
你怎麼找到這個的
We stole it from the police depot. Why?
從警方那裡偷來的 為什麼
This looks like the exhaust system from an F-27.
看似是F27拆下來的排氣系統
No. It's the prototype for Robo's flight pack.
它是機械員警的飛行裝置藍本
The funding ran out before we got a chance to test it.
在我們測試它前 經費就耗盡了
- How do you know so much about it?  - I designed it.
- 你怎麼知道這麼多  - 是我設計的
Well, looks like the odds on the home team just went up.
看來我們取勝的機會增大了
What I've done is programmed the command system...
它會聽從你的...
to take its cues from your hard drive.
硬體指揮
I've also rigged it to work as an auxiliary power unit.
我還把它改裝成一個輔助驅進器
So if you ever have a power drain like yesterday...
如果你的動力下降...
...just interface with the flight pack and recharge whether you fly or not.
只要接上飛行裝置再充電就行
Nikko, see those resistors over there?
看到那些電阻器嗎
Get them for me, will you?
麻煩你給我 好嗎
Get them for me.
替我抓他們
Promise me.
答應我
Get them for me.
替我抓他們
Promise me.
答應我
What's going on?
什麼事
Excuse me.
對不起
Hey, where you going?
你去哪裡
Unfinished business.
做未做完的事
It's okay. He'll be back.
不要緊 他會回來的
He needs us too.
他也需要我們
Where's he going?
他要去哪裡
To keep a promise.
履行承諾
You got a Robocop. You got an alien cop?
你們有個機械員警 有沒有外星人員警
- Got a ghost cop?  - I don't have time for...
- 有沒有幽靈員警  - 我沒有時間...
You got a vampire cop?
有沒有吸血殭屍員警
- Murphy.  - Good evening, Sergeant Reed.
- 墨菲  - 晚安 瑞德警官
Do you know there's a warrant out for your arrest?
你可知道有拘捕令要逮捕你
Yes.
知道
I was just checking. What can I do for you?
我問問罷了 有什麼可以效勞
Please direct me to the Rehab Staging Area.
請指示我建改隊試點的位置
It's down the hall. You can't miss it.
在走廊前端 你會找到的
Thank you.
謝謝你
You may want to call the fire department.
你可能要通知消防隊了
- You got a light?  - Sure, man.
- 有沒有火  - 有的
Allow me, scum.
讓我來吧 混蛋
Oh, shit.
該死
盤問狀態
Where's McDaggett?
保羅·麥代格在哪裡
That does not look like a police station.
那裡不像一間警察局
You're damn right I'm not at the station.
對 我不是在警察局裡
If my spy hadrt warned me, I'd be dead now.
如果不是我的探子警告我 我現在已經死了
I thought your damn ninja was supposed to take care of Robocop.
我以為你那個該死的忍者 會對付機械員警
That's the deal. I clear the area, he keeps the robot off my back.
說好了 我清理那一區 他就不讓那個機械人找我麻煩
You have the device I sent you?
你有沒有我調派給你的裝置
It hasn't come to that yet. And it won't. Relax.
還不用那個 也不會用 放鬆點
It is difficult for me to continue our business relationship...
若我不清楚你的做法
...when I don't know your methods.
我們很難合作下去的
You don't need to know my methods.
你不必知道我的做法
I said I'll clear the area and I'll clear it.
我一定會清理那一區
Just get the robot cop off my back.
你別讓那個機械員警煩我就是了
I understand you're willing to pay good money to know where the rebel base is.
我知道你會付厚酬 去得到叛軍總部的地點
Yes, well...
是的
...the money's good...
報酬很豐厚
...if the tip's good.
如果情報準確的話
The last tip saved your ass, didn't it?
上次的情報救了你一命 是吧
What do we have here?
這裡有什麼
You don't like men in uniform?
你不喜歡穿制服的男人
My dad lost his job. I just need some money.
我爸爸剛失業 我需要一點錢罷了
- We've got lots of money, honey.  - Don't.
- 我們有錢  - 不要
- No!  - She said, "No."
- 不要  - 她說不要
Maybe you have a hearing problem?
你們聽覺有問題嗎
Go home, young lady.
小姐 回家吧
You are in violation of curfew.
你違反了宵禁條例
Where's McDaggett?
保羅·麥代格在哪裡
Room 212.
212號房
Thank you.
謝謝你
I hope you are insured.
我希望你買了保險
Elevator door sticks!
電梯門壞的
Don't.
不要
I have a message from officer Lewis.
路易士警員托我帶個話給你
Stop!
停車
Drive!
開車
I said, drive, goddamn it, drive!
我叫你開車
My time, my money. I told you and won't tell you again, understand?
我的時間 金錢 我不會再說了 明白嗎
I must commandeer your vehicle for police use.
我要徵用你的汽車作警方用途
What is your problem, sucker?
你有什麼問題 混蛋
I mean, officer.
我是指... 長官
Cover me.
掩護我
Commander!
指揮官
警告: 兒童在玩耍
What's the deal?
什麼事
Where the hell is Robocop?
機械員警去了哪裡
We could drive around and listen for explosions.
我們可以開車聽一下哪裡有爆炸聲
Are you doing that?
是你做的嗎
I got tired of splicing wires, so I put in a pulse tach decoder.
我厭倦了焊接電線 所以放進一個脈衝流速解碼器
- Telemetric?  - No.
- 搖測的  - 不是
- Smart ass.  - I know you are, but what am I?
- 真聰明  - 你才聰明 我算得上什麼
Here, let me try.
讓我試試
Thanks for the heart attack.
你嚇我們一跳
I believe I will go and send out a recon team.
我會派遣一支偵察隊出去
I got a better idea.
我有個更好的方法
Why don't we just all have a seat.
不如我們都坐下來
And relax.
和放鬆
It'll all be over in a few minutes.
幾分鐘內就會結束
You son of a bitch.
你這個混蛋
Watch the language, there's children present.
小心說話 有孩子在場
Drop it, Coontz.
放下它 康斯
I'm not going to ask twice.
我不會重複說的
What do you mean, "it'll all be over in a few minutes"?
你是什麼意思"幾分鐘內就結束"
Get the kids out of here! Now!
快帶孩子們離開 快點
Bertha!
貝黛
Go.
走
- Got to get her.  - Go!
- 要去救她  - 快走
Come on, let's go! Come on!
來吧 快走
Come on.
來吧
Come on! Get in! Come on!
快點 進去
Come on!
快點
Okay, now go!
好了 走吧
- Go on!  - No, it's happening again!
- 快走  - 不 又再發生了
Don't let them take you away.
別讓他們把你帶走
I said, go! Get out of here!
我叫你走
Where is he?
他在哪裡
Go to hell.
去死吧
Take her to headquarters.
帶她去總部
I promise my men won't leave a mark on you.
我的手下不會在你身上留下痕跡
Sir. What about our friend Coontz?
長官 我們的朋友康斯又怎樣
If we'd let him live, we'd have to have paid him.
若我們讓他活著就要付錢給他
We're talking about hundreds of thousands of dollars in damage.
我是說會損失數十萬元
- Murphy can be rough on properties.  - Yeah. Well...
- 墨菲對財物不留情的  - 很好
...every cent of it will be coming out of your salaries.
每分每毫的損失 都由你的薪水中扣除
Hey! You built him!
是你們製造他的
We're taking Cadillac Heights.
我們要進佔卡迪拉克區
I'll need 50 of your men armed and in full body armor in one hour. Johnson...
我要你50個手下 一小時後全副武裝候命
...tell the CEO the demolition crews will have access at 06:00 hours tomorrow.
告訴總裁 拆卸人員明早六點可以進入
Hey, we don't do that kind of work.
我們不做那類工作
That was a direct order, sergeant.
這是個直接命令
Driving people out of their homes is no work for a cop!
把市民逐出家園 不是員警的工作
Now, sergeant.
警官
Fifteen years on the force is quite an investment.
在警隊工作15年是一項投資
Your job, your pension.
你的工作 你的退休金
Maybe instead of worrying about these squatters, think about your own family.
別擔心那些擅闖者了 想想你的家人吧
I am.
我有想
I'm thinking I have to go home and face them.
我正在想我要回家面對他們
You can't do this.
你們不能這樣做
You are employees of oCP!
你們是OCP的雇員
Now remember that.
記著
You're jeopardizing your retirement benefits!
你們在危害自己的退休福利
Stop that man.
截住那個人
How would you and your friends like to make some money?
你和你的朋友們可想賺點錢
- It's...  - Johnny...
- 這是...  - 強尼...
- Rehab!  - Hurray!
- 建改隊  - 好
Johnny Rehab action figures, parts and accessories all sold separately.
強尼建改隊人像 配件和服飾個別發售
Three nuns and five clergy are dead...
在被認為是機械員警的 最新暴行中...
...in what is believed to be the latest atrocity by the killer cyborg, Robocop.
有三名修女和五名神職人員喪生
The OCP claim the former police unit...
OCP宣稱該名前度警員...
...is responsible for a spree of terrorism...
在底特律市舊城的卡迪拉克區...
...in the Cadillac Heights section of Old Detroit.
引發一輪恐怖活動
I'm sorry, I can't even read this.
抱歉 我不能讀這個
This is bullshit! Are you buying this?
簡直胡說八道 你相信它嗎
Are you kidding me? Robocop?
你開玩笑嘛 機械戰警
（臨時故障）
Marie.
瑪莉
Lousy sons of bitches!
混帳
- OCP bastards!  - Nobody is listening to you, sweetheart.
- 神經病混蛋  - 沒有人會聽的
We are in position.
我們各就各位
This is Big Stick. You have a green. Arm and proceed to strike zone.
這是大棍 準備就緒 帶齊武器進入攻擊區
All teams, we have a green.
所有隊伍 準備就緒
Hey, take it easy.
放鬆點
- So what now?  - What now?
- 現在怎麼辦  - 怎麼辦
- Game's over, Moreno. Just shut up.  - What about Bertha's plan?
- 完蛋了 閉嘴吧  - 貝黛的計畫又如何
Damn it! Bertha's dead!
該死 貝黛已經死了
I'm sorry.
對不起
Folks, in about 45 minutes...
各位 大約45分鐘後...
...the Rehabs are coming to blow you out of your neighborhood.
建改隊就會來對付你們
I want you to take your kids...
帶你們的孩子...
...and anybody who shouldn't be fighting to the basement!
和任何不能作戰的人到地下室
The rest of you are hereby deputized by the Detroit Police Department.
其餘的人就受底特律員警部委派
It's time to show how real cops kick ass.
是時候給他們看看員警的厲害
Detroit Police! Identify yourself.
底特律員警 出示你的身分
You are under arrest for assaulting an officer.
你因為襲警被拘捕了
And destruction of police property.
還有破壞警方財物
動力能量低 需要下載能量
Quiet!
肅靜
Hold your fire until absolutely necessary.
別開火 直到有絕對需要
Commander...
指揮官...
...Detroit Police are out there, sir. They're fighting against us.
長官 底特律警方在外面 他們在反抗我們
So? We have a schedule to keep.
那又如何 我們要依期行事的
We don't fire on police officers! You're out of line, McDaggett.
我們不可向員警開火 你太過分了
I'm in charge here. I'm pulling the plug.
我是指揮 由我做主
Sit down.
坐下
Have you gone war-wacky?
你打仗打瘋了
I said, sit down.
我叫你坐下
Good idea.
好主意
How are we getting out of here anyway?
我們怎樣離開這裡
How'd you get...? Never mind.
你怎樣... 算了吧
Is there a transmission dish outside?
外面有沒有傳訊碟形天線
Yeah, and I was just watching the Media Break guy pick his nose.
有 我還看到新聞追擊 那個傢夥挖鼻孔呢
Do you have your computer with you?
你有電腦嗎
People of Detroit...
底特律的市民...
...this is an illegal broadcast. It may be cut off at any time.
這是非法廣播 它隨時會被截斷
So listen to me.
所以聽我說
OCP is lying to you.
OCP在欺騙你們
They're destroying people's lives for big business.
他們為了大生意而殺害生命
Those Rehabs you see on TV...
在電視上的那些建改隊...
...they're mercenaries hired by OCP to throw people out of their homes.
他們是OCP聘用的雇傭兵 要把市民逐出家園
You've got to believe me.
你們要相信我
I'm speaking for all the homeless and jobless citizens of this city...
我代表本市所有無家可歸者 失業者...
...and every city like it run by heartless capitalist scumbags...
和每個受資產主義混蛋管治的城市發言
OCP doesn't care about people. OCP cares about...
OCP不關心市民
Your neighborhood is next unless you fight back now.
反抗吧 否則你的鄰居就是下一個
Time's running out. OCP's the enemy.
沒時間了 OCP就是敵人
I repeat. Time is running out. OCP is the enemy.
時間不多了 OCP就是敵人
Help us. Innocent people are dying.
無辜市民正在死去
- More ammo!  - More ammo!
- 給我子彈  - 給我子彈
Zack's hit!
澤克中槍了
They're winning, aren't they, sergeant?
他們會贏 是不是
What in the name...?
那是什麼
瞄準中 聰明炸彈已接合
Sir?
長官
Splatter that, you sons of bitches!
來吧 你們這班混蛋
Come in, Big Stick.
大棍 請通話
All right, Mr. Robocop.
好吧 機械員警先生
Come and get me.
來抓我吧
Get away from the door.
別靠近那扇門
Think it over.
考慮一下
Oh, my God, Johnson, our stock has dropped to nothing.
我的天 股價跌至零了
We're ruined.
我們完蛋了
How may I help you, officer?
警員 有什麼可以效勞
By resisting arrest.
拒捕
Don't count on it, chum.
休想
Anyway, what's the charge?
控罪是什麼
The murder of Anne Lewis.
謀殺安妮·路易士
Dead or alive, you're coming with me.
不管死活 你也要束手就擒
McDaggett, you can have OCP. It's all yours. Sayonara.
你可以要了OCP 它是你的了 再見
Where're you going?
你去哪裡
You're gonna miss all the fun.
你會錯過好戲的
No flashy bravery, tin man.
別逞強了
Or the two cuties say, "Bye-bye."
否則那兩個可人兒會說再見
What are you doing?
你幹什麼
Stop them! Stop them!
制止他們
Stupid fools!
蠢才
Don't you know what you've done to us?!
你可知道你做了什麼
Those androids are programmed with a thermal fail-safe device.
那些機械人裝有 熱能故障安全設備
You mean to self-destruct?
你是指自動毀滅
In 15 seconds, everything within 20 yards...
在15秒內 所有二十碼內的東西...
...of where we're standing will be atomized.
都會粉碎
We're dead, you stupid slag.
你們死定了 笨蛋
Don't count on it, chum.
休想
Hang on.
堅持住
- Come on.  - Let me give you a hand.
- 算了  - 讓我幫你
Kanemitsu-san...
金光先生
...I realize that it looks bad...
我明白情況很糟糕
...but maybe our plans were over-ambitious.
可能我們的計畫野心過大
Let's start a skoshy bit smaller.
我們再合作較小規模的吧
Let's gentrify this neighborhood. Build strip malls.
讓我們美化這地區 興建商場...
Fast-food chains. Lots of popular entertainment. What do you think?
速食連鎖店 大量娛樂設施 你認為怎樣
- What did he say?  - You're fired.
- 他說什麼  - 你被開除了
I got to hand it to you.
我得謝謝你
What do they call you?
他們叫你做什麼
Murphy, is it?
墨菲 是不是
My friends call me Murphy.
我的朋友們叫我墨菲
You call me...
你就叫我...
...Robocop.
機械員警